It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
어지러운 전국 시대.
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
Musashi is here-dasu!
무사시 등장이오!
Karakuri Kengouden
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
A man always dreams of the day
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
in the center of the world to become
제일 강해질 날을
AH! AH! the strongest
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
모험의 길의 막을 연다
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
Go! Fight!
가라! 싸워라!
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
Tomorrow will be glorious
내일은 빛난다
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Fight the utmost with the stillness
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
His eyes shined! Musashi!
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
Shutentiger was forcing the villagers to work to mine alluvial gold.
슈텐타이거는 사금을 얻기 위해 마을 사람들에게 노동을 강제하고 있었다.
Musashi and Kojirō responded to Santa's wish by making Shutentiger explode after a intense fight.
무사시, 코지로는 산타의 부탁을 들어 격심한 전투 끝에 슈텐타이거를 대폭발시켰다.
Woah!
히익!
It's Ishimatsu's Ghost!
이시마츠의 유령이오
Our characters have stopped at a hot spring to relieve their strain of travelling.
여행을 계속하던 일행은 노독을 풀기 위해 온천에 들렀다.
Hot springs are the best no matter what.
뭐가 어쨌더라도 온천이 제일이구나.
Hey, Kojirō, let's get into the hot spring too-dasu.
저기, 코지로, 우리도 온천에 들어가오.
What if Senhime gets attacked? Do you think we have time to enjoy something at leisure?
센히메 님이 습격당하면 어쩔 셈이냐? 그런 태평한 일할 틈이 있을 것 같냐!
Hmm, then I'll join Osenchan in the bath and stand watch-dasu.
흠, 그럼 나, 오센짱하고 같이 탕에 들어가서 망보겠소.
I- idiot! Don't you know your etiquette?
바, 바보야! 너, 예의도 모르냐!
I'm just doing what I have to-dasu.
해야 할 일을 할 뿐이오.
Then!
그럼!
I told you.
말했잖아.
We don't even have to protect her if she's that strong-dasu...
이렇게 강하면 지킬 필요 없소...
Musashi!
무사시!
This is one gloomy inn-dasu.
왠지 기분 나쁜 여관이오.
What is it, Musashi? Are you scared?
뭐냐, 무사시. 무섭냐?
T- that's not it-dasu!
그, 그런 건 아니오!
But aren't you shivering your knees?
그래도 무릎을 떨고 있잖아.
T- t- this is because the dinner is late-dasu.
이, 이, 이건 저녁이 늦어서 떨고 있는 것이오.
Princess, watch out!
공주님, 조심하세요!
Dinner is ready.
식사 가져왔습니다.
Oh, it was just the inn owner-dasu! Please don't scare us like that-dasu!
뭣이오, 단지 여관 주인이었소! 놀래키지 않았으면 좋겠소!
Aren't you a coward, Musashi.
무사시 정말 겁쟁이구나.
N- no, that isn't it-dasu. I was just like, "Wow, the food is finally here!"-dasu!
아, 아니오. 방금 그건 우와, 겨우 요리가 나왔다! 이었을 뿐이오.
I was so hungry-dasu! I'll eat as much as... I... wanted-dasu...
아, 정말 배고팠소! 잔뜩 먹겠...소...
I- is this all you have-dasu?
이, 이것밖에 없소?
Even a diet menu would be more than this.
다이어트 메뉴도 이것보다는 많을 거야.
Isn't this too much?
이건 좀 지나치지 않아?
I'm sorry. But this is the best cooking available.
미안합니다. 그렇지만 이게 드릴 수 있는 최고의 요리입니다.
It seems that he has something to tell. Would you like to share your story with us?
뭔가 사정이 있는 것 같군. 괜찮으시다면 말씀해주시지 않겠습니까.
Yes. There is a mountain named Osorezan near this village, and it is told that spirits gather in there.
예. 사실은 이 마을 가까이에 공산(恐山)이라는 영혼이 모이는 산이 있습니다.
Recently at there, the departed spirits of fleeing soldiers have appeared and raged.
그 곳에 최근 목이 없는 패잔 무사의 망령이 나타나 날뛰었습니다.
The villagers were scared and left the village, and this inn is the only remaining here.
아주 겁에 질린 마을 사람들은 이곳저곳 마을을 떠나, 남아 있는 건 이 여관 하나뿐입니다.
Those are really bad ghosts. Alright, we will get rid of those ghosts.
아주 못된 유령이네. 용서할 수 없어. 좋아, 그 유령을 퇴치해 주겠어.
Really?
정말입니까?
J- j- just a moment, Osenchan! That's too dangerous-dasu!
자자잠깐, 오센짱, 그건 어떻게 봐도 위험하오!
Hey, I never said that I'm going to do that myself. It's you who's going to wipe them out. You will.
어라, 내가 한다고는 한 적 없어. 네가 퇴치할 거야, 네가.
I... I will?
저... 나이오?
-Are you scared? -Err, no way-dasu.
-무섭니? -에이, 설마이오.
That's right! Musashi is an excellent martial artist!
그렇지! 무사시는 훌륭한 무예가지!
It's good if you know that-dasu.
알았다면 됐소.
That ghost does not have eyes, a neck, or anything, and will appear like this...
그 유령, 눈도 목도 아무것도 없는 주제에 이렇게 나타나.
Aren't you a scardycat, Musashi.
거 무사시도 참, 이런 이야기에 약하다니까.
Osenchan, I don't care about dinner anymore, so please let us sleep now-dasu...
오센짱, 밥은 이제 됐으니까 빨리 자오.
Nope! This is a rare chance to see ghosts with my bare eyes. Do you think I can sleep without missing that chance?
싫어. 겨우 유령을 볼 수 있는 기회인데. 안 보고 잘 수 있을 것 같니?
Don't you agree, Kojirō?
그렇지, 코지로?
Kojirō, aren't you scared?
코지로? 넌 무섭지 않아?
Yes. Coincidentally, I don't believe in ghosts at the moment.
예. 저는 마침 유령이란 걸 믿지 않아서요.
Then you go take ghosts down-dasu.
그럼 유령을 퇴치하시오.
My objective is to protect Senhime. Nothing more or less than that.
나는 센히메 님을 호위하는 게 사명. 그 이상도 이하도 아니다.
I see that you're scared too, Kojirō-dasu.
역시 코지로도 겁에 질렸소.
This means that ghosts will show up soon. Then...
이런 때는 분명 유령이 나올 것입니다. 그럼 저는...
Night!
그럼 이만.
Hey, inn owner!
아, 주인!
It just became interesting.
재밌어졌네.
How-dasu...
어째서이오...
Go, Musashi, Kojirō!
가자, 무사시, 코지로!
B- before that, let me go to toilet-dasu!
아, 그 전에 잠깐 화장실에 갔다 오겠소!
Musashi!
무사시!
Musashi...
무사시...
I suddenly wanted to pee because it became scary-dasu...
이게 무서워지니까 오줌이 매려져서 안 되겠소.
W- w- who is that-dasu?!
누, 누, 누구이오!
Hey, why are dangos here? Kojirō sure grant me my wish sometimes-dasu!
어라, 왜 이런 곳에 단고... 코지로 놈도 참, 가끔은 소원도 들어주오!
If he's with something to eat, he should tell me as-is-dasu.
먹을 게 있으면 고분고분히 말하면 될 것이오.
Thank you for this!
잘 먹겠소!
H- huh?
어, 어라?
Huh, it moved that far while I wasn't looking at-dasu.
어라, 못 본 새에 저기까지 갔소.
Huh? Hey, stop-dasu! You're one active dangos!
어라? 어이, 멈추시오! 거 참 활기찬 단고오!
I knew it. Musashi ran away because he was scared.
정말, 무사시도 참. 진짜로 무서워서 도망쳤나 봐.
Hey, Musashi!
어, 무사시!
Hey, wait-dasu!
어이, 멈추시오!
He has no courage whatsoever.
저 자식 참 근성 없는 놈이야.
No, something looks very wrong with him.
아니요, 뭔가 모습이 이상합니다.
-Huh? -Let's follow him.
-어? -따라갑시다.
I wonder where did that dango-chan hide to.
거 참, 단고쨩 어디로 숨었소...
Hey, Musashi! Long time no see!
어이, 무사시! 오랜만이다!
M- Mr. Ishimatsu!
이, 이시마츠 씨!
Ishimatsu was like an older brother of Musashi.
이시마츠는 무사시에게 형과 같은 존재였다.
Heya!
어이!
B- but, Mr. Ishimatsu, you were supposed to be dead...
그, 그래도, 이시마츠 씨는 죽었을 텐데...
Yeah, just as you see, I'm a ghost.
뭐, 보는 대로 내가 유령이지.
It's been a long time, and this is how you treat me, bro?
오랜만에 만났는데 좀 차갑지 않냐, 형제?
Mr. Ishimatsu, you haven't changed at all from when you were living...
이시마츠 씨, 살아 있을 때부터 이런 느낌이었으니...
Did you get lost and couldn't rest in peace-dasu?
역시 길을 잃어서 성불 못한 것이오?
You idiot! The road to the other world is one step away; you simply cannot get lost!
이 자슥! 저 세상에 가는 길이라는 건 길을 잘못 찾기조차 어려울 정도로 눈 앞에 있어!
But, you know, walking that path alone is somewhat lonely.
그래도 말야, 그 길을 나 혼자서 걸어가는 건 왠지 외로워서 말야.
Musashi, wouldn't you like to go with me?
무사시, 나하고 같이 가지 않을래?
Huh? Are you telling me to die-dasu?
어? 나보고 죽으란 것이오?
Right!
그렇지!
I- I can't accept that wish even if it's Mr. Ishimatsu's one.
그, 그건 아무리 이시마츠 씨의 부탁이라 해도 들어줄 수 없소.
The dangos that we ate back then was great...
그 때 먹은 단고는 맛있었지...
You're right-dasu!
그렇소!
If you didn't mess up back then, I would be living instead of being dead.
그 때, 니가 그 짓거리 안 했으면 난 안 죽고 살아 있었겠지.
I am really sorry about what happened back then-dasu.
그 때는 정말 미안했소.
But you know, it's all good memories now!
그래도 말야, 지금은 다 좋은 추억이야!
How's this, Musashi? Wouldn't you like to travel by two with me like how we did back then?
어떠냐, 무사시! 다시 그 때처럼 둘이서 즐겁게 여행할 생각 없냐!
B- but! Dying is still scary-dasu...
그, 그래도! 나, 죽는 건 역시 무섭소.
How spiritless are you? I guess you'd be satisfied if we die together!
거 참 패기도 없는 놈이군. 그럼 나하고 같이 죽으면 불만 없겠지?
That's it-dasu! That will work perfectly-dasu!
그렇소! 그렇게 하면 딱 좋소!
Alright! Then let's hurry!
좋아! 그럼 서두르자!
I'll count; let's jump off when I say one, two, and three!
그럼 내가 수를 셀 테니까, 하나, 둘, 셋 하면 뛰어내리자!
Got it-dasu!
알겠소!
Then let's do this! One...
그럼 가자! 하나...
Two and...
둘에...
-Three -Errr
-셋 -이랴아
Are you okay, Mr. Ishimatsu?
괜찮소, 이시마츠 씨?
Erm, f- forget about me! It could have been better if you jumped down right away.
아, 나, 나는 신경쓰지 마라! 바로 뛰어내렸으면 좋았을 텐데.
No, I can't let Mr. Ishimatsu be alone and be lonely!
아니아니, 더는 이시마츠 씨를 혼자 있도록 냅둘 수는 없소!
Aren't you cumbersome...
성가신 놈이구나.
Alright! Let's brace ourselves up and try this again!
좋아! 마음을 다잡고 다시 한번 가자!
One!
하나!
Two and...
둘에!
Three
셋
Huh? Mr. Ishimatsu, why aren't you jumping off-dasu?
어라? 이시마츠 씨 왜 안 뛰어내리오?
U- uh, that is...
아, 아니, 그건 말야...
I have something to ask you, Mr. Ishimatsu-dasu.
나, 이시마츠 씨에게 질문이 있소.
What is it?
뭐냐?
Can a ghost die twice-dasu?
유령이라는 건 두 번도 죽을 수 있소?
I- idiot! For my cute younger brother, I can die multiple times!
이, 이 자슥! 귀여운 아우인 너를 위해서라면 난 몇 번이라도 죽을 수 있어!
That was it-dasu! You thought about me that much-dasu!
그런 것이었소! 그렇게나 날 생각해줬던 것이오!
Hey, watch out!
어이, 위험하잖아!
Musashi, nevermind about whatever; let's just jump off!
무사시, 잡소리는 생각하지 말고 서둘러 뛰어내리자!
-Musashi!
-무사시!
Oh, right. I must bid farewell to those two-dasu!
그렇소! 저 둘한테 작별의 인사를 해야 하오!
Dammit! Just die already!
에잇, 어서 죽어라!
What the-?! Who's there?!
뭐야? 누구냐!
Musashi!
무사시!
More and more interference!
방해꾼이군!
-Musashi! -Say something if you're there!
-무사시! -있으면 있다고 답을 해!
I'm here-dasu! Hey!
나 여기 있소! 어이!
-Musashi! -What in the world are you doing?
-무사시! -너 대체 뭐하냐?
Are you an idiot or what? Who in the world would be lured by a ghost and ask that ghost to die together?
너 정말 바보구나. 대체 세상에 유령에게 꾀여서 쉽게 죽자고 하는 사람이 있냐!
But I cannot refuse Mr. Ishimatsu's favor when we are a brother by blood-dasu...
그래도, 나, 피를 나눈 이시마츠 씨의 부탁은 거절할 수 없소.
That Ishimatsu's ghost... Isn't something weird?
그 이시마츠의 유령, 이상하지 않니?
Weird?
이상하오?
You said you were kicked away hard. Does a ghost ever do that?
너, 걷어차였다고 했지? 유령이 그런 짓을 하냐?
That's true-dasu, but...
그건 그렇지만...
Moreover, who threw the rope that saved your life?
게다가 널 구한 줄은 대체 누가 던졌어?
Dunno...
그러게...
According to my hunch, all the answer should be at that Osorezan.
내 예감으로는 그 답은 전부 공산에 있을 것 같다.
What kind of secret is hidden in that Osorezan? Wait for the stormy latter half!
공산에 숨겨진 비밀은 무엇인가? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Wow. This lukewarm wind... It feels like something's about to show up.
와, 뜨뜻미지근한 바람이 부는 게 분명 뭐가 나올 것 같은 분위기야.
What's going on?
아니, 이건 대체...
Kojirō! Osenchan! Where are you-dasu?!
코지로! 오센짱! 어디이오!
I'm here!
난 여기 있어!
-Senhime! -I'm here too!
-센히메 님! -나도 여기 있어!
Huh?
응?
Senhime! Musashi! You'd better not move here until the fog clears up.
센히메 님! 무사시! 여긴 안개가 갤 때까지 움직이지 않는 게 좋아요.
-Let's wait for now! -Got it!
-일단 기다립시다! -그래!
Roger-dasu!
알겠소!
Huh? Is it Kojirō?
어? 코지로이오?
-Hey, Musashi. -Mr. Ishimatsu!
-어이, 무사시. -이시마츠 씨!
Musashi! Even though we've failed yesterday, let's go to the other world today as friends!
무사시, 어제는 실패했지만 오늘은 사이좋게 저 세상에 가자!
You know... I don't want to die-dasu.
저, 그게... 나는 역시 죽는 건 싫소.
The dangos that we ate back then was great...
그 때 먹은 단고는 맛있었지...
It was great-dasu!
맛있었소!
Just like how we did back then, I'd love to share the impression with you.
그 때하고 똑같이, 나는 그 감동을 너하고 나누고 싶어.
Mr. Ishimatsu! You're so kind-dasu!
이시마츠 씨, 정말 다정한 분이오!
Musashi! We will be able to die properly this time.
자, 무사시! 이번엔 틀림없이 죽을 수 있을 거야.
Y- you're right.
그, 그렇소.
Let's do this properly today!
자, 오늘은 똑바로 가자!
Got it-dasu.
알겠소.
Before that...
일단 그 전에...
W- what are you doing?
뭐, 뭔 짓이냐.
By this, we will be able to jump down together without any mistake-dasu.
이렇게 하면 실패할 일 없이 같이 뛰어내릴 수 있소.
What?!
머?!
Let's go-dasu.
자, 이제 가오.
Uh, that is... M- Musashi, I... I don't like to be tied like this.
그, 그게, 무사시, 나, 이렇게 묶여 있는 건 별로 좋아하지 않아.
Please don't do that.
관두자.
If you're gonna die, your preferences don't matter-dasu!
죽을 거라면 좋고 싫고 관계 없소!
Let's go-dasu!
가소!
Y- you know, can't you just tie it lightly so that I can pull my hand out?
이, 있잖아, 조금만 묶어서 스을쩍 손이 빠지게 하지 않을래?
No way-dasu.
안 되오.
T- then, wouldn't you like to fall from somewhere more relaxing that we can fall more softly?
그, 그럼, 좀만 사알짝 떨어질 수 있도록 좀 안심되는 곳에서 떨어지지 않을래?
Then we can't die!
그러면 못 죽소!
Give it up like an adult!
어른답게 포기하고 단념하시오!
I- idiot! Stop it!
머, 멍청아! 그만해!
Y- you brat!
이, 이 꼬맹이가!
W- what are you doing-dasu, Mr. Ishimatsu?!
뭐, 뭔 짓이오, 이시마츠 씨!
Are you okay, Musashi?!
괜찮냐, 무사시!
Huh?
어?
You bastards!
네 이놈!
Hey, Mr. Ishimatsu!
어, 이시마츠 씨!
Musashi, you dimwit! I told you he's not a ghost!
무사시, 이 멍청한 새꺄! 저 놈은 유령이 아니랬지!
But I can't leave Mr. Ishimatsu like that-dasu!
그래도! 저런 이시마츠 씨를 그냥 두고 볼 수는 없소!
Even if that Ishimatsu is a ghost, your friendship is fishy.
저 이시마츠가 유령이라고 해도, 너희 우정은 수상하구나.
If Ishimatsu really couldn't die properly, then make him rest in peace with your power!
정말 이시마츠가 죽지 못했다면, 무사시, 네 힘으로 성불시켜 줘라!
Isn't that the true friendship to your dead friend?!
그게 죽은 친구에게의 참된 우정 아니냐!
Yes, you're right-dasu.
아, 그렇소.
Senhime, this has been bothering me; this Osorezan seems to be calling people towards it.
센히메 님, 계속 신경쓰이는 게 있는데, 이 공산은 사람들을 불러들이고 있는 것 같습니다.
Osenchan!
오센짱!
Help me!
살려줘!
Mr. Ishimatsu!
이시마츠 씨!
Musashi! I took your comrade to prevent us from being interrupted! Now, let us cross Sanzu River all together!
무사시! 이번엔 방해받지 않게 동료를 데려왔다! 자, 다 함께 같이 삼도내를 건너자!
What's this?! Let me go! Let me go!
뭐야, 이거! 관둬! 그만해!
Mr. Ishimatsu! I get that you're lonely, but I want you to cross the Sanzu by yourself-dasu.
이시마츠 씨! 외로운 건 알겠는데 삼도내는 혼자서 건너길 바라오.
The dangos that we ate back then was great...
그 때 먹은 단고는 맛있었지...
-That's right-dasu! -Musashi!
-그랬었소! -무사시!
You'd better listen to me!
넌 내가 말하는 걸 듣는 게 낫다!
What's this? Were the dangos you ate back then bad actually?!
뭐야? 너, 그 때 단고가실은 맛없었던 거냐!
It was great, but I will give you a greater punch-dasu!
맛있었지만 그것보다도 더 맛있는 펀치를 내가 주겠소!
I will have you rest in peace with my hands-dasu, Mr. Ishimatsu!
이시마츠 씨는 내가 성불해 주겠소!
Well, thank you!
그건 고맙다!
Mr. Ishimatsu, when did you learn techniques like this-dasu?!
이시마츠 씨, 언제 이런 기술을 배웠소?
In the other world.
저 세상에서 배웠지.
Kojirō!
코지로!
Die, Musashi!
죽어라, 무사시!
W- who is it?!
누, 누구냐!
Musashi, you must not be fooled.
무사시 님. 속으면 안 됩니다.
This guy is not someone named Ishimatsu.
이 자는 이시마츠라는 자가 아닙니다.
Mr. Jūbee!
주베 씨!
Musashi, see for yourself about who this guy actually is!
무사시 님. 이 녀석의 정체를 똑똑히 봐 두십시오!
You are Onihime!
넌 오니히메!
Jūbee, you bastard! It was so close and you dared to butt in!
네 이놈, 주베! 눈 앞이었는데 잘도 방해했겠다!
Remember this!
기억해 둬라!
Mr. Jūbee. What brought you here?
주베 님. 어째서 여기에?
We'll talk about that later. For now, let's chase Onihime.
그 이야기는 나중에. 일단 서둘러 오니히메를 쫓읍시다.
I knew it.
역시 그랬군.
Mr. Jūbee, what did you know-dasu?
주베 씨, 뭐가 역시이오?
To tell you the truth, not too long ago, General Ieyasu has broken down because of a high fever of unknown reason.
사실은 얼마 전, 제너럴 이에야스 님이 원인 불명의 고열로 쓰러졌습니다.
What? My grandpa?
어? 할아버지가?
Numerous doctors couldn't find out the reason. That's why we asked a shaman for a purification,
의사들이 얼마고 알아보아도 원인을 알 수 없었습니다. 그래서 기도사에게 점을 치도록 했더니,
and we found that there is a spiritual wave from the north side that is cursing General Ieyasu.
북쪽에서 이에야스 님에게 저주를 거는 영파가 발생하고 있다는 결과가 나왔습니다.
You're saying that it's that-dasu, right?
그게 저것이란 소리오.
No doubt about it.
틀림없이.
Then the disturbance in the village too?
그럼 마을에서의 유령 소란도 역시...?
When I looked around this place, everything was because of Onihime's sorcery.
이 장소에 대해 알아보니, 전부 오니히메가 건 요술이었습니다.
Onihime?
오니히메?
The time has come for you to not hold back. Send all the spiritual wave from Osorezan to General Ieyasu.
너희들, 이젠 살살 할 필요가 없다. 공산의 모든 영파를 제너럴 이에야스에게 보내라.
The world will be ours!
천하를 우리에게!
Playing with humans' minds, and even trying to fiddle with General Ieyasu is unforgivable!
인간의 마음을 가지고 노는 것도, 제너럴 이에야스에게까지 손을 뻗치는 건 용서할 수 없소!
Mr. Jūbee and Kojirō! We will do something with that sorcery-dasu!
주베 씨, 코지로! 저 주술, 어떻게든 조치해 주겠소!
Do your best, everyone!
힘내, 모두!
Onihime! I will not forgive for what you did to me-dasu!
오니히메! 네놈의 악행은 내가 용서하지 않겠소!
No use with interference!
방해는 소용없다!
Most of all, you dared to play with my precious memories!
무엇보다도 내 소중한 추억을 가지고 놀았겠소!
Hmph, it's your fault for even treating those preciously.
흥, 그런 걸 소중하게 여긴 네 잘못이다.
I will not forgive you-dasu!
용서할 수 없소!
Everyone! Take care of all of them at once!
너희들, 한방에 이 녀석들을 쫒아버려라!
How impudent!
이런 건방진!
Mr. Jūbee!
주베 씨!
If you're going with a whirlwind, then I'm going with a whirlwind, too!
젠장, 그 쪽이 회오리라면 이 쪽에서도 회오리로 승부이오!
Niten'ichiryū: Tornado Sword!
이천일류, 회오리검!
That was excellent, Musashi!
훌륭합니다, 무사시 님!
You bastard!
네 이놈!
Onihime!
오니히메!
Give it up, Onihime! There is no precedent of praising the evil!
포기해라, 오니히메! 악행을 찬양했던 선례는 없다!
Shut up!
에이, 닥쳐라!
Hiding your beautiful face, why are you doing the evil?
아름다운 얼굴을 숨기고서 뭘 위해 이런 악행을 하나.
Hmph! You will never understand what's in my mind!
흥, 넌 내 기분을 절대 알지 못할 테다!
Remember this. I will pay this back!
기억해 둬라. 이 복수는 꼭 하겠다!
Do not run away, Onihime!
도망치지 마시오, 오니히메!
Stop, Musashi!
멈춰라, 무사시!
What?
뭣이오?
Hm?
어?
Then I'll be going now. Senhime and both of you, be careful.
그럼 저는 여기까지. 센히메 님도 어느 쪽도 조심하세요.
Thank you, Jūbee. Musashi, let me tell you all the scary stories during our way.
고마워, 주베. 자, 무사시. 도중에 무서운 이야기 잔뜩 해 줄게.
Please don't do that-dasu!
그건 하지 말아 주시오!
It isn't scary when it's bright, you know!
낮이라면 무섭지 않잖아?
-No, that's not the problem-dasu! -Hey, Musashi! At a graveyard around this place...
-아니, 그런 문제가 아니오! -저기, 무사시! 이 주변에 있는 무덤에...
Ahhh! I don't want to listen-dasu!
으악! 듣고 싶지 않소!
The enemy's attack that deranged Musashi's mind is gone. Now, to the intense evil hands of Hanzō... Go, go, Musashi!
무사시의 마음을 어지럽힌 적의 공격은 갔다. 점점 치열해지는 한조의 마의 손에... 가라, 가라, 무사시!
Do not lose, Musashi! Keep going on with your stormy journey!
지지 마라, 무사시! 질풍노도의 여행을 계속해라!
Sometimes the moon jumps over
허공의 주머니에 달이
the pocket of empty sky
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
Laugh loudly and
큰 소리로 웃으면
morning will come tomorrow
내일에는 아침이 와
Don't worry too much about losing
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Keep going! Go for it!
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
A bare hand is strong
맨손은 강해
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how life is! Look, a chance
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
follows us wagging its tail!
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
Winter is the ideal of men-dasu. And it is not the time to act like a gentleman-dasu.
겨울은 사내의 로망이오. 하고 점잔 뺄 때가 아니오.
I don't feel so good because of seasickness-dasu.
나, 뱃멀미로 기분이 안 좋소.
Misfortune comes after another; this time, Onigoroshi, who uses a Karakuri shark, has appeared-dasu.
엎친 데 덮친 격으로 이번엔 카라쿠리 상어를 쓰는 해적, 오니고로시가 나타났소.
With Daisuke, we rode on a transportation ship-dasu.
다이스케하고 손을 잡아, 우리는 한번 운송선에 타게 되었소.
Next story! The Sea is Scary - It's Onigoroshi!
다음 이야기! 바다는 무섭네, 오니고로시이오
It's time for a stormy revenge-dasu!
질풍노도의 복수이오!
Next Episode
다음 이야기
The Sea is Scary
바다는 무섭네
It's Onigoroshi
오니고로시이오
Look forwards for it!
기대하세요!